you can ask kind of these, you know,
laughing chuckle um or like emotions
kind of excited shouting and so maybe we
can play that.
I'm not sure actually we I'm not doing
this again.
That's a good point.
We didn't can I share the audio on this
stream?
Uh such a such a beginner mistake I've
I've been doing this so often and I was
like, yeah, there's a livestream.
We should have audio.
Uh if I pipe the audio out on the HDMI,
are you able to hear it on the stream?
Or do we need like a separate do we have
anyone?
Anyone? Yeah. Um, yeah, maybe we we might
need to translate that for um for for for
tech. Come on. Please.
I promise you'll love this one.
Works. Nope. No, no, no.
Never again. The last 10 weren't funny.
The next 10 won't be funny.
You're not funny and you never will be.
How many 11 labs engineers does it take to
screw a light bulb?
Oh my god. I'm going home.
So, you can see kind of the lines are are
blurring now because um you know,
wickedly uh evil laugh.
Maybe we'll listen to this one.
Oh. The ocean smell that lads?
That's the scent of freedom.
And just a hint of mutiny.
Now, grab your cutlasses stow your fear.
Tonight we dine like kings.
Or we sink like legends.
Ha ha ha. Now, imagine your customer
support sounds like that.
Now, that's you know, that's a support
agent that you want to talk to, right?
Um, so, but yeah, what you can see here is
you know, we we our research
focuses on kind of anything audio.
And we're looking to sort of build this
omni model that can basically